deploybot.com 2019-07-09

# DeployBot Privacy Policy

**Effective: 1/24/2018**  

This Privacy Policy applies to the website(s): [www.deploybot.com](https://www.deploybot.com/) owned and operated by SaaS.group, LLC (collectively, “SaaS.group”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). This Privacy Policy describes how SaaS.group collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide, as well as the human resources data transferred to us for processing on behalf of our customers. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. 

### EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks

SaaS.group, LLC complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework [as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome) regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. SaaS.group, LLC has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

SaaS.group is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf.  SaaS.group complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions. 

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, SaaS.group is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.  In certain situations, SaaS.group may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, SaaS.group, LLC commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact SaaS.group, LLC at: 

support@deploybot.com

SaaS.group, LLC has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, you may visit <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield> for more information or to file a complaint (free of charge). To facilitate fast and convenient resolution of complaints, you agree to participate in on-line dispute resolution through JAMS Online Mediation (Endispute). 

Under certain conditions, Privacy Shield provides the right to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have not provided resolution. This is described in [Annex I to the Privacy Shield](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction).

**Collection:**

We may collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Contact Information, such as name, email address, mailing address, or phone number; 
  * Demographic information, such as age, education, gender, interests and zip code
  * Billing Information, such as credit card number and billing address; 
  * Unique Identifiers, such as username, account number or password; 
  * Geo location based on IP address;
  * Information about your business, such as company name, company size, business type.

We may also collect, from you, personal information about your contacts such as Name and email address where we can send receipts of your purchases. When you provide us with personal information about your contacts we will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided. If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at the contact information below. 

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site. 

SaaS.group and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. 

**Use:**

The personal information as indicated being collected above is used for billing, identification, authentication, service improvement, research, and contact. 

### Information Sharing

1.     With Third Parties: 

We may share your information with third-party business partners, for instance, for the purpose of enhancing our products and services. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at the contact information below.

2.     With Service Providers: 

We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities.  These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us, to which these services may include: 

  * Payment processing
  * Providing customer service
  * Sending marketing communications
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Providing cloud computing infrastructure

3.     With Public Authorities or Law Enforcement: 

In certain situations, SaaS.group may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, when we believe there is a violation to our [Terms of Service](https://deploybot.com/tos), protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. If SaaS.group is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information. We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. SaaS.group, LLC ensures that all source code, files and data remain private and confidential. Due to the sensitive nature of source code we take this very seriously and make it our primary concern for all customers. We restrict access to personal information to SaaS.group employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our service. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at the contact information below. We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. 

### Access 

Upon request SaaS.group will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by logging into your account or by contacting us at the contact information below. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. In certain circumstances we may be required by law to retain your personal information, or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing a service. 

SaaS.group, LLC acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. SaaS.group has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct their query to the SaaS.group, LLC’s Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe. In certain circumstances we may be required by law to retain your personal information, or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing a service. 

### Choice 

We partner with a third party to display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

You may sign-up to receive email or newsletter or other communications from us.  If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may update your email preferences by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you or by contacting us at the contact information below.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy 

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

### Privacy Questions / Feedback 

If you have questions or concerns about SaaS.group’s Privacy Policy please contact us at [support@deploybot.com](mailto:support@deploybot.com) or 304 S. Jones Blvd #1205, Las Vegas, NV, 89107.
